<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About the Package
================================
KVM (for Kernel-based Virtual Machine) is a full virtualization solution for Linux on x86 hardware containing virtualization extensions (Intel VT or AMD-V). It consists of a loadable kernel module, kvm.ko, that provides the core virtualization infrastructure and a processor specific module, kvm-intel.ko or kvm-amd.ko. Using KVM, one can run multiple virtual machines running unmodified Linux or Windows images. Each virtual machine has private virtualized hardware: a network card, disk, graphics adapter, etc.

=Supported versions=
QEMU emulator version 2.2.0
=Setup=
The Agent must be installed on KVM enabled machine.
=Setup= 
* API version and https port can be configured in this VARA based on your environment.
=Common Inputs=
(None)
=Actions=
Following actions are supported.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.CLONE_VM
* Action Description:  Clone a VM from an existing VM.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.LIST_VMS
* Action Description: List VMs from an existing VM.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_VM
* Action Description: Delete VM from existing VM.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.GET_VM_INFO
* Action Description:  Retrieves VM information.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.REBOOT_VM
* Action Description:  Reboot VM from existing VMs.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_VM
* Action Description:  Create a new VM.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.RESET_VM
* Action Description:  Reset a vm immediately without any guest shutdown.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.START_VM
* Action Description:  Start a guest domain, either from the last managedsave state, or via a fresh boot if no managedsave state is present.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_NETWORK
* Action Description:  Creates a network, using settings from an XML file.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.LIST_NETWORKS
* Action Description: Lists the virtual networks libvirt is aware of, along with basic status and autostart information.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.STOP_VM
* Action Description: Stop a VM.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.GET_NETWORK_INFO
* Action Description:  Displays basic information for a virtual network.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.SAVE_VM_TO_FILE
* Action Description:  Saves a running domain ( RAM , but not disk state) to a state file.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.RESTORE_VM_FROM_FILE
* Action Description:  Restores a  VM (domain) from provided source file.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.SHUTDOWN_VM
* Action Description:  Gracefully shuts down a domain.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.START_NETWORK
* Action Description:  Starts an inactive, previously defined, virtual network.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.RESUME_VM
* Action Description:  Moves a VM out of the suspended state.

* Action name:   PCK.AUTOMIC_KVM.PUB.ACTION.SUSPEND_VM
* Action Description:  Suspend a running VM.]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>